
[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/AppDev/trip%20app/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 10.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/9.0.0/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
